Speaker 1: that I genuinely feel like when you break up with someone and you have a crazy ex, that was how it felt like being fired from a daily wire. Daily wire. Daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. From a daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. Andrew Klavan. Andrew Klavan. My crazy ex-boyfriend, Andrew Klavan. The daily wire. Is that the daily wire? He does
Speaker 2: some stuff. The daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. At the
Speaker 1: daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. From a daily wire. The daily wire. The daily wire. From a daily wire. Take the daily wire. The daily wire. Ben Shapiro. Ben Shapiro. Dave Smith.
Speaker 1: answer to this question
Speaker 3: might get you kicked off the daily wire i had to laugh at that that's really funny the daily wire i'm a daily wire my psycho
Speaker 4: ex-boyfriend daily wire daily wire daily wire reagan conrad jeremy boring the daily wire daily wire daily wire daily wire with the daily wire and the daily wire daily wire
Speaker 1: brett cooper out at the daily wire daily wire the daily wire the daily wire the daily wire the daily wire the daily wire daily wire sign up for the daily wire i got fired from the daily wire we're like she's done she's toast the daily wire the daily wire daily
Speaker 5: wire ben shapiro fuck you and the midget horse that you rode in on and
i
Speaker 6: was like why are you so obsessed with
me